var spanish = [
	{
		front: "the boy",
		back: "el chico"
	}, {
		front: "the girl",
		back: "la chica"
	}, {
		front: "the man",
		back: "el hombre"
	},{
		front: "the woman",
		back: "la mujer"
	}, {
		front: "the family",
		back: "la familia"
	}, {
		front: "the house",
		back: "la casa"
	}, {
		front: "the food",
		back: "la comida"
	}, {
		front: "hello",
		back: "hola"
	}, {
		front: "good morning",
		back: "buenos dias"
	}, {
		front: "good evening",
		back: "buenos tardes"
	}, {
		front: "goodbye",
		back: "adios"
	}, {
		front: "please",
		back: "por favor"
	}, {
		front: "thank you",
		back: "gracias"
	}
];

module.exports = spanish;